

ANDROID DEVELOPER · SOFTWARE ENGINEER · DATA SCIENTIS

Faculty of Computer Engineering and Science, Shahid Beheshti University, Tehran, Iran

🛘 (+98) 991-277-5711 | 🗷 kamyababedi@gmail.com | 🏕 www.kamyababedi.com | 🗗 KamyabAbedi | 🗖 KamyabAbedi

## **Summary**\_

Current I'm third year student of CE at Shahid Beheshti University and interested in Back-end programming, IT security, ML and other geek stuff. 2+ years experience specializing in the Android development, plus 1 years experience using Adobe XD. Super nerd who loves Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises. I'm passionate about my work. Because I love what I do, I have a steady source of motivation that drives me to do my best

### **Education**

### Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, Shahid Beheshti University

Tehran, Irai

B.Sc. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Sep.2018 - PRESENT

- During my degree at Shahid Beheshti University I learnt lots of key skills such as team work and project management. Although we mainly focused on software development and the principles of programming I use a lot of these skills to my advantage in my day to day work.
- Received full scholarship from Shahid Beheshti University(tuition waiver).
- · One of Iran's 4 top universities.
- · Supervisor: Dr. Hamid Reza Mahdiani
- · Cumulative GPA: 3/4

#### **Shahid Beheshti High School**

Tehran Iran

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA IN MATH AND PHYSICS

Sep. 2014 - Sep. 2018

- Received full scholarship from Shahid Beheshti School(tuition waiver).
- · Cumulative GPA: 3.85/4

## Work Experience

#### **Jahad Daneshgahi Institute**

Tehran, Iran

TEACHER
Top ship a Fundamental of programina

Sep. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- Teaching Fundamental of programing.
- · Determined and graded homework, computer assignments and final projects.
- · Under the supervision of Dr.Jahedi.

### **Shahid Beheshti University**

Tehran, Iran

TEACHING ASSISTSNT, TECHNICAL WRITING AND PRESENTATION COURSE

Feb. 2021 - PRESENT

- Held TA sessions.
- Determined and graded homework, computer assignments.
- Under the supervision of **Dr. Neshati**.

#### **Shahid Beheshti University**

Tehran, Iran

TEACHING ASSISTSNT, FUNDAMENTAL OF PROGRAMING COURSE

Sep. 2019 - Feb. 2020

- Managed the TA Group for this semesters and changed the TA class syllabus to teach new students Android Development.
- · Held TA sessions.
- Determined and graded homework, computer assignments and final projects.
- Under the supervision of **Dr. Abdoos**.

### **Android Developer**

Iran

FREELANCE

Sep. 2019, PRESENT

• I was asked to update an existing Android app to the latest version of Android and to fix any issues caused by this as well as a few other existing

## **Honors & Awards**

Ranked within the top 1%, among 170,000 participants in the annual Iranian University Entrance Exam for Bachelor's degree.

Tehran, Iran

2017 **Ranked within the top 10 GPAs**, among the 500 Students of the Math and Physics program at Shahid Beheshti School.

Tehran, Iran

MAY 30, 2021 KAMYAB ABEDI · RÉSUMÉ 1

#### COMPETITIVE PROGRAMMING

2020 Ranked 68th, among 800 contestants, Code Star, Programming Contest in Quera website.

2021 **Ranked 75th**, among 1328 contestants, Code Star, Front-end Contest in Quera website.

Tehran, Iran Tehran, Iran

# **Project**

### "2 Cars" game by Ketchapp - C++

MINI PROJECT OF ITP COURSE

Nov. 2018

- implement 2 cars game with SDL library.
- Used SDL and SBDL library that designed to provide low level access to audio, keyboard, mouse, joystick, and graphics hardware via OpenGL and Direct3D. It is used by video playback software, emulators, and popular games including Valve's award winning catalog and many Humble Bundle games.
- ITP course, **Dr. Sadegh Aliakbary**, Shahid Beheshti University.

#### "Doodle jump" game by Lima Sky - C++

MINI PROJECT OF ITP COURSE

Nov. 2018

- implement Doodle jump game with SDL library.
- Used SDL and SBDL library that designed to provide low level access to audio, keyboard, mouse, joystick, and graphics hardware via OpenGL and Direct3D. It is used by video playback software, emulators, and popular games including Valve's award winning catalog and many Humble Bundle games.
- ITP course, **Dr. Sadegh Aliakbary**, Shahid Beheshti University.

### "Jetpack Joyride" game by Halfbrick Studios - C++

PROJECT OF ITP COURSE

Nov. 2018

- implement Jetpack Joyride game with SDL library.
  Used SDL and SBDL library that designed to provide low level access to audio, keyboard, mouse, joystick, and graphics hardware via OpenGL
- and Direct3D. It is used by video playback software, emulators, and popular games including Valve's award winning catalog and many Humble Bundle games.
- ITP course, **Dr. Sadegh Aliakbary**, Shahid Beheshti University.

### "Lidingeram" Messenger Application - Java

PROJECT OF AP COURSE

Jul. 2018

- developed a messenger application for Android phones.
- Used socket programming.
- AP course, **Dr. Mojtaba Vahidi**, Shahid Beheshti University.

#### library management system - Java

PROJECT OF DS COURSE

Jul. 2019

- Design and Implementation of Library Management System.
- Used KD-tree and Trie Data Structures
- that was an application for assisting a librarian in managing a book library in a university. The system would provide basic set of features to add/update members, add/update books, and manage check in specifications for the systems based on the client's statement of need.
- Data structure course, Dr. Ahmad Ali Abin, Shahid Beheshti University.

#### "Othello" game - Python

PROJECT OF AI COURSE

Jul. 2020

- Implementation of smart agent for Othello game.
- Used Alpha-beta pruning and Minimax algorithm.
- Artificial Intelligence and Expert Systems course, **Dr. Armin Salimi-Badr**, Shahid Beheshti University.

#### **Decaf Compiler - Java**

PROJECT OF COMPILER COURSE Jul. 2021

- Implementation a compiler for decaf language. Decaf is a simple small object-oriented language similar to C/C++/Java languages.
- Used lexer/scanner generator, LALR parser generator.
- Compiler course, **Dr. Ghassem Jaberipur**, Shahid Beheshti University.

#### The Matson Evaluation of Social Skills - Python

PROJECT OF DATA MINING COURSE

Jul. 2021

- The Matson Evaluation of Social Skills with Youngsters(MESSY) and its Adaptation for Iranian children and adolescents.
- Data Mining course, **Dr. Alireza Talebpoor**, Shahid Beheshti University.



### **Programming Languages:**

Java (Advanced), C/C++ (Advanced), Python (Intermediate), JavaScript (Intermediate), Go(Intermediate), MATLAB(Intermediate), VHDL (Intermediate), Verilog (Intermediate), Assembly(Fair).

### **Other Languages:**

HTML/CSS (Intermediate), SQL (Fair).

#### **Databases:**

MySQL (Intermediate), MongoDB (Intermediate).

### Other:

Git (Advanced).

## Workshops & Courses \_\_\_\_\_

2020	Structuring Machine Learning Projects Course, Prof. Andrew NG.	Coursera Website
2020	<b>Developing Android Apps Course</b> , some Android course by Google.	Udacity Website
2020	The Hands On Machine Learning Cours, Learn and understand Machine Learning from scratch.	Udemy Website
2019	Human-Centered Design, by University of California San Diego.	Coursera Website

## Languages\_

- Persian (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- German (Elementary)

# **Memberships**\_

- **Member of the Student Scientific Association,** Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, Shahid Beheshti University
- **Member of the Mobile Development Group,** Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, Shahid Beheshti University